Guide to the Russell Van Nest Black papers, 1919-1968.
Black, Russell Van Nest papers
- Series I. Correspondence
  - 1935
    - C General, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Housing. PWA. Landscape profession. Housing; Public Housing with Bibliography. USSR Urbanization. Harold Dodds, Svetozar Drahomanov.
    - Cornell University, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      Professional Practice. Gilmore Clark.
    - D General, 1934-1936 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      New Jersey. Public Housing; Housing. Bibliography; Urbanization. USSR. Harold Dodds, Svetozar Drahomanov
    - Delaware Valley Protective Association, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      Park Planning - Roosevelt Park, Pennsylvania.
    - D Prospects, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - E General, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      School Planning Convention. Columbia University.
    - Edgewater, New Jersey, 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      Zonging. William Conway. Zoning Commission.
    - Englewood, New Jersey, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      Zoning.
    - E Prospects, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      Elmira, N.Y.; Madeville, Waxman, Buck, Teeter and Harpending, Attorneys at Law.
    - Expense Account Correspondence. National Resources Board, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - F General, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      George Farny.
    - F Prospects, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      Farmville, Virginia.
    - G General, 1925,1935 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      Recreational Planning - Passaic, New Jersey. Elizabeth Graham. Passaic Valley Flood Control Commission.
    - H General, 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      St Paul, Minnesota; Virginia. Planning Practice; Plans and Maps; Housing. Personal Correspondence. Edward Hartman; Justin Hartzog; Henry Hubbard.
    - Harvard University Correspondence- file, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      Alfred Bettman; Howard Menhinick
    - Housing Division FKWA, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      Housing. Federal Emergency Administration of Public Works.
    - J General, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - K General, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - L General, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - George La Monte, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      Bound Brook, New Jersey. Borough Planning Board - Bound Brook.
    - Land Subdivision Manual, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      CIP Membership; Land Subdivision Manual. Harland Bartholomew
    - Leonia City Plan, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 26)
      MIT Planning Course. Leonia, New Jersey.
    - M General, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 27)
      Small Plants v Big Plants. Lewis Mumford)
    - M Prospects, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 28)
      Mt. Olive, New Jersey. Henry Wright.
    - MIT, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 29)
      Planning Course. Frederick Adams.
    - N General, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 30)
      Housing Conference. John Nolen. Joint National Conference on Housing.
    - New Jersey Municipalities Magazine and Correspondence, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Bernard Newman, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 32)
      Philadelphia Housing Association.
    - O General, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Office (Insurance, etc.), 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 34)
      Professional Society ASPO. Alfred Bettman. Treasury Department; American Society of Planning Official.
    - P General, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Pennsylvania State Planning Board, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 36)
      Alfred Bettman. National Resources Board
    - R General, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 37)
      Public Relief. Robert Randall.
    - R Prospects, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 38)
      Satellite Cities. Warren Vinton. Resettlement Administration.
    - Resettlement Administration, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 39)
      Bound Brook Project (New Jersey). Albert Mayer.
    - S General, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 40)
      Annual Economics Conference for Engineers. Stevens Institute of Technology.
    - T General, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 41)
      Housing; Public Works. Armand Tibbitts.
    - V General, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 42)
      Lawrence Veiller. National Resources Committee.
    - Virginia State Planning Board, 1934-1936 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - W General, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 44)
      Professional Practice; Harry Wallis; Henry Wright. League of Virginia Municipalities.
    - W Prospects, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - 1935-1936
    - Aero Service Corporation; Kaufman, 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - American Planning and Civic Association, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - American Society of Civil Engineers, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 48)
      John Nolen.
    - American Society of Landscape Architects, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 49)
      City Planning. Deming Tilgon
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 50)
      Practice. Alfred Bettman.
    - Applications for Work, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - B General, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 52)
      Planning Boards; Educational Planning; Urban Planning Study Outline. Zoning and Physical Spaces.The American City. American Society of Planning officials.
    - Bridgewater Township, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 53)
      Bridgewater, New Jersey.
    - Bucks County Farm, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 54)
      Commonwealth of Pennsylvania; Department of Highways and Princeton Bank and Trust Company.
    - B - file, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 55)
      Buffalo, NY.
    - C General, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 56)
      Planning Education Harvard. Gilmore Clark; Jacob Crane.
    - Cornell University, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 57)
      City Planning Education. Livingston Farrand; Gilmore Clark; George Young.
    - D General, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 58)
      Harold Dodds
    - Delaware Valley Protective Association, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 59)
      Rural Electrification Administration.
    - E General, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Edgewater, New Jersey, 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Englewood, New Jersey, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 62)
      Highway Planning - Maps; Clippings; Correspondence.
    - E Prospects, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 63)
      Elmira, New York.
    - Expense Account (National Resources Committee, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 64)
      Transactions.
    - F General, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 65)
      Includes Personal Correspondence.
    - William Flemer, Jr, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - G General, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - G Prospects, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - H General, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 69)
      Planning Education. Harvard. Community Planning Research. Henry Hubbard; J. B. Conant; Max Wehrly.
    - Investments, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 70)
      Business Investments. A. V. Dawes.
    - K General, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - L General, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 72)
      La Monte Estate.
    - Leonia City Plan, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 73)
      Leonia, New Jersey. Zoning. Jesse Leslie
    - L Prospects, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 74)
      Lynchburg, Virginia. City Planning Commission.
    - M General, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 76)
      Planning Education. MIT Lecture Series. School of Architecture.
    - Mount Olive Township, New Jersey, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 77)
      Zoning. Mt. Olive Township Planning Board.
    - N General, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - National Resources Board, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      Educational Planning - Pennsylvania; New Jersey. National Planning Program. Robert Randall; L. Deming Tilton
    - National Youth Administration, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - New Jersey Planning Board, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 81)
      Recreational Planning. Mary Jane Green. National Resources Committee
    - N Prospects, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 82)
      Brunswick, New Jersey. Planning Education. Rutgers University
    - National Planning Board, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 83)
      Physical Planning Research Report.
    - New Jersey Municipalities Magazine and League, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 84)
      Relief Program
    - O General, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 85)
      Olean, New York. Chamber of Commerce.
    - Office (Insurance, etc.), 1936 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - P General, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 87)
      Princeton, New Jersey. Building Plan.
    - P Prospects, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 88)
      New Brunswick, New Jersey; Passaic, New Jersey.
    - Pennsylvania State Planning Board, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 89)
      Delaware River Basin. National Resources Committee
    - Public Works Administration, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 90)
      Housing. Federal Emergency Administration of Public Works.; American Society of Planning Officials.
    - R General, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 91)
      Rochester, New York. Robert Randall.
    - Resettlement Administration, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 92)
      Rural Relief Program; Resettlement Program, Information Releases.
    - Rural Electrification Administration, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - S General, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      Clarence Stein. Includes Personal Correspondence
    - T General, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      Armand Tibbitts.
    - U General, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      Planning Society. City Planning Institute Meeting Oct. 18, 1936. Raymond Unwin; John Nolen.
    - Virginia State Planning Board, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - W General, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      Practice. Includes Personal Correspondence.
    - Works Progress Administration, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 1937-1938
    - A General, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      Tracy Augur.
    - American Planning and Civic Association, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      Planning Legislation.
    - American Society of Civil Engineers, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      National Mapping; Blighted Areas; Zoning; Underground Utilities; L. J. Carmalt "Rural Zoning as an Adjunct to State Highway Improvement".
    - American Society of Landscape Architects, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      Committee of National Planning.
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      City Planning Society
    - Applications for Work, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - B General, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      West Orange, New Jersey. Federal Aid; Robert Weinberg "For Better Places to Park," The American City. Zoning. Alfred Bettman; Frederick Bigger; Lemuel Black; Harold Buttenheim
    - Bridgewater Township, New Jersey, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      Bridgewater, New Jersey. Zoning. J. H. McMurray. Bridgewater Township Planning Board.
    - William M. Bristol, Westfield Project, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      Westfield Development Plan. Lonsdale Green, Jr.; William Bristol
    - Bucks County Farm, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      Includes personal correspondence
    - C General, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      Western Reserve University, Cleveland, Ohio. Gilmore Clark; Arthur Coney. Solebury Cooperative Association.
    - Columbia University, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 19)
      Planning Education. Carl Feiss. Raymond Unwin
    - Cornell University, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 20)
      Planning Education. Gilmore Clark.
    - C Prospects, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 21)
      Charleston, West Virginia. City of Charleston.
    - D General, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 22)
      New Jersey. Harold Dodds.
    - Delaware Valley Protective Association, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - E General, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Edgewater, New Jersey, 1935, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 25)
      Zoning. Board of Commerce, Navigation
    - E Prospects, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Educational Plans, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 27)
      Planning Education, Gilmore Clark. An Experiment in Education in Planning. American City Planning Institute; American Society of Planning Officials.
    - Expense Account Correspondence, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 28)
      National Resources Committee.
    - F General, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - William Flemer, Jr, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - G General, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 31)
      Conservation Society, The Garden Club of America.
    - H General, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 32)
      Planning Education. Harvard. Henry Hubbard; B. Antrim Haldeman.
    - Harvard University, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 33)
      Park Planning. Planning Education.
    - I General, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Investments, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - J General, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - K General, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - L General, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - L Prospects, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 39)
      Long Branch, New Jersey. Zoning. City Planning Board.
    - George La Monte, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 40)
      Bound Brook, New Jersey. Land Development. La Monte Estate. George La Monte and Son.
    - M General, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 41)
      Mexico. John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation.
    - M Prospects, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 43)
      Planning Education. Frederick Adams
    - Middlesex County, New Jersey, 1939-1937 (Box 8, Folder 44)
      New Brunswick, New Jersey. Henry Jeffers.
    - Mount Olive Township, New Jersey, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 45)
      William Lucas; Kelly Stroyk.
    - N General, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 46)
      New Brunswick, New Jersey.
    - National Resources Committee, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 47)
      New Jersey; Pennsylvania.
    - New Jersey League of Municipalities, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - New Jersey State Planning Board, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - N Prospects, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - O Prospects, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 51)
      Orlando, Florida. Linton Allen.
    - Office Insurance, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - P General, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 53)
      Pennsylvania State College. Planning Education.
    - Passaic, New Jersey, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 54)
      Zoning. Passaic City Planning Commission.
    - Pennsylvania State Planning Board, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Planning Education, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 56)
      Robert Randall; Gilmore Clark; William Emerson; H. V. Hubbard; Harold Lautner; Alfred Bettman; Bob Randall. American City Planning Institute.
    - Princeton Board and Township, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 57)
      Princeton, New Jersey. Zoning.
    - Princeton Institute for Advanced Study, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 58)
      New Jersey. Land Development.
    - Programs of Conference Arrangements, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 59)
      American City Planning Institute Programs; City Planning Society. Tracy Augur; Jacob Crane; Arthur Comey.
    - Public Housing Administration, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 60)
      Federal Housing Administration.
    - R General, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 61)
      Includes Personal Correspondence. Robert Randall.
    - Resettlement Administration, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 62)
      New Jersey.
    - S General, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 63)
      Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania. Clarence Stein, Howard Strong.
    - T General, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 64)
      Includes Personal Correspondence. Armand Tibbitts.
    - U General, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 65)
      Includes Personal Correspondence. Raymond Unwin.
    - V General, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 66)
      Includes Personal Correspondence. Lawrence Veiller.
    - W General, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 67)
      New Jersey. American Society of Planning Officials. Henry Wright; Paul Walsh.
    - Walker-Gordon Farm, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - W Prospects, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 69)
      Wildwood, New Jersey; Wilmington, Delaware. Zoning. Ward H. Bright.
    - Z General, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - A General, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      American Planning and Civic Association; Education. New York Adult Education Council.
    - Aero Service Corporation, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Agenda: Rules, Purposes, Policies, National Resources Committee, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - American Society of Civil Engineers, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      Land Subdivision Manual of the City Planning Division. Frederick Bigger.
    - American Society of Landscape Architects, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Landscape Architecture Education.
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1936-1938 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      Housing. City Planning Practices. John Nolen.
    - A Prospects, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      City Planning Practice.
    - Applications for Work, 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      Massachusetts Institute of Technology..
    - B General, 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      Bucks County, Pennsylvania; Pittsfield, Massachusetts. Zoning; Housing. Russell Black "The County- An Effective Unit for Planning". Russell Bourne; Alfred Bettman; Frederick Bigger.
    - Bucks County Farm, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      Personal Business.
    - B Prospects, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      Bucks, Pennsylvania.
    - Bridgewater Township, New Jersey, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      Bridgewater Township Planning Board.
    - C General, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      Arthur Comey; Jacob Crane; Randolph Cautley; Gilmore Clark.
    - C Prospects, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      Charleston, West Virginia. Hugh Miller Association, Inc.
    - Cornell University, 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      Gilmore Clark
    - D General, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Delaware Valley Protective Association, 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - E General, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      Low Cost Housing. American Eugenics Society.
    - Englewood, New Jersey, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - E Prospects, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      Borough of Emmaus.
    - F Prospects, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      Franklin, New Jersey.
    - William Flemer, Jr, 1936, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      Recreational Planning - New Jersey.
    - G Prospects, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      Garfield, New Jersey. City of Garfield.
    - H General, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 24)
      Justin Hartzog; Henry Hubbard; Curtis Hitchcock; B. A. Haldeman.
    - Harvard University, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 25)
      Planning Education. Arthur Comey.
    - H Prospects, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 26)
      Haskell, New Jersey. Haskell Improvement Co.
    - I General, undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
      International Geographic Congress. E. S. Draper.
    - Investments, 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      Correspondence and Pamphlets.
    - Archie R. Joy, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 29)
      "Lake George Business". Edward McKernon; Archie Joy.
    - K General, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 30)
      Lower Makefield Township, Pennsylvania. Zoning.
    - L General, 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 31)
      Red Bank, New Jersey. Planning Practice; Land Development.
    - George La Monte Estate, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 32)
      La Monte Estate Subdivision. George La Monte and Son.
    - Leonia, New Jersey, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 33)
      Planning Practice.
    - L Prospects, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 34)
      Leonia, New Jersey; Los Angeles, California. Zoning. James O. Stevenson.
    - Long Branch, New Jersey, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 35)
      City Planning Board.
    - M General, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 36)
      Princeton, New Jersey. Planning Education. Albert Mayer; Frederick Adams.
    - M Prospects, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 37)
      Madison, New Jersey. Zoning. Harold Buttenheim.
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 38)
      Frederick Adams.
    - Mount Olive Township, New Jersey, 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - N General, 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 40)
      New Hope, Pennsylvania. WPA Arts Project; Housing. National Housing Committees; Federal Relief. National Assocation of Housing Officials.
    - N Prospects, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 41)
      New Rochelle, New York. Zoning. City of New Rochelle.
    - National Resources Committee, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - New Jersey State Planning Board, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 43)
      Highway Planning; Indiana. Alfred Bettman. National Resources Committee.
    - Office (Insurance, etc.), 1938 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - P General, 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 45)
      New Hope, Pennsylvania. Water Supply System.
    - Passaic, New Jersey, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 46)
      City Planning Commission.
    - Pennsylvania State Planning Board, 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Personal Mary A. Black, 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Princeton Borough and Township, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 49)
      Princeton, New Jersey. Zoning. Borough of Princeton.
    - P Prospects, 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 50)
      Scotch Plains, New Jersey; Princeton, New Jersey. Zoning. Hetfield & Hetfield; Borough of Princeton.
    - R General, 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 51)
      Pittsfield, Massachusetts
    - S General, 1937-1937 (Box 9, Folder 52)
      New Jersey. Howard Strong; Clarence Stein
    - Solebury Cooperative Association, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 53)
      Discount Food Program.
    - S Prospects, 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 54)
      Seaford, Delaware; Sheffield, Pennsylvania. Zoning.
    - T General, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - T Prospects, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 56)
      Teaneck, New Jersey. Township of Teaneck.
    - U General, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 57)
      New Jersey. Housing. United States Housing Authority.
    - W General, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 58)
      Washington; Oregon; Bucks County, Pennsylvania. Housing; Zoning; Highways. Lewis Mumford; Coleman Woodbury. Woulley Real Estate
    - W Prospects, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 59)
      Warren, Pennsylvania. Zoning.
    - Y Prospects, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - 1936-1939
    - A General, 1938-1939 (Box 9, Folder 61)
      New Jersey; New York. Sewage Disposal. The American Public Health Association
    - Aero Service Corporation, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - American City Planning Institute, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - American City Planning Institute, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 64)
      Washington, D.C.. City Planning Practice. William Parker; Frederick Bigger; Arthur Comey; Frederick Adams; Tarcy Augur. American Institute of Planners. Planning Education.
    - American City Planning Institute Membership Committee, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 65)
      Planning Society. Alfred Bettman; Gilmore Clark.
    - American Planning and Civic Association, 1938-1939 (Box 9, Folder 66)
      National Planning.
    - American Society of Civil Engineers, 1938-1940 (Box 9, Folder 67)
      Membership
    - American Society of Landscape Architects, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 68)
      Lawrence Sheridan.
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 69)
      Planning Education. Walter Blucher.
    - A Prospects (Allentown), 1939 (Box 9, Folder 70)
      Allentown, Pennsylvania. City Planning Commission.
    - Applications for Work, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - B General, 1938-1940 (Box 9, Folder 72)
      Pennsylvania; Pittsfield, Massachusetts. Zoning Highway Planning. Robert Moses. Fred Bigger; Alfred Bettman. The American City.
    - Bridgewater Township, New Jersey, 1938-1939 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - B Prospects, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 74)
      Park Planning Bucks County, Pennsylvania ;Bangor, Pennsylvania; Bound Brook, New Jersey. Bucks County Association; Commonweath of Pennsylvania State, Planning Board.
    - Bucks County Farm, 1938-1940 (Box 9, Folder 75)
      Cooper Pidcock (Real Estate and Insurance.)
    - C General, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 76)
      Planning Practice. Routine Personal Correspondence.
    - CPI (City Planning Institute) Committees on Reorganization, 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 77)
      City Planning Societies. Arthur Comey; Alfred Bettman; Jacob Crane.
    - Cornell University, 1939-1940 (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - C Prospects, 1938-1939 (Box 9, Folder 79)
      Cap May County, New Jersey. Samuel Wetherill
    - D General, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 80)
      New Jersey. Harold Dodds. Princeton University.
    - Delaware Valley Conference, 1937-1939 (Box 9, Folder 81)
      Recreational Planning - New Jersey; Delaware Valley. H. Dodds. State of New Jersey National Resources Committee.
    - D Prospects, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 82)
      Recretional Planning - Delaware and Raritan Canal Propery.
    - E General, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 83)
      Routine Personal Correspondence.
    - Expense Account Correspondence; Natural Resource Planning Board., undated (Box 9, Folder 84)
      City Planning and Vouchers.
    - F General, 1934-1935;1938-1939 (Box 9, Folder 85)
      Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Zoning. Princeton Nurseries; Fedeal Housing Administration.
    - G General, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 86)
      Tuscon, Arizona. Mary Green. Tuscon Regional Plan, Inc.